<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Trouble with Travis</title>
    <link>https://www.thetroublewithtravis.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Trouble with Travis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:09:04 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.thetroublewithtravis.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Annual Albums</title>
      <link>https://www.thetroublewithtravis.com/posts/annual_albums/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:09:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.thetroublewithtravis.com/posts/annual_albums/</guid>
      
      <description>Introduction Since 2014 I&amp;rsquo;ve been keeping a chronicle of albums. This is typically music that I find during that year, or that was relevant to me in some way personally. This page serves as a chronicle of those albums so the songs are not lost. As a rule, album titles and songs are locked after the year&amp;rsquo;s end.
Annual Albums Pathfinder (2025) Fruit Bat - Of Monsters and Men Road Regrets - Dan Mangan The Blue, The Green - Lonely The Brave Open Passageways - All Them Witches Money Game, Pt.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fuck Wells Fargo</title>
      <link>https://www.thetroublewithtravis.com/posts/fuck_wells_fargo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 20:25:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.thetroublewithtravis.com/posts/fuck_wells_fargo/</guid>
      
      <description>Once upon a time, I was very young. I got a job. That job asked me to get a bank so they could deposit their checks directly to me. Young, independent, and so very sure of myself I walked into a Wells Fargo. They opened a checking account for me, and everything was fine. The job didn&amp;rsquo;t last long. I counted every penny as every penny was precious.
So it was really weird when I checked my account and it was over drafted by $100 dollars.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>...but why?</title>
      <link>https://www.thetroublewithtravis.com/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.thetroublewithtravis.com/pages/about/</guid>
      
      <description>Like most things, this all started to see if I could.
See, I&amp;rsquo;d had this idea for The Trouble with Travis a long time ago. It would be a blog space, where I&amp;rsquo;d explore (and probably fumble a bit) through some writings and just get it out there. See where it lead. But there were several problems with how I&amp;rsquo;d set it up.
Well, not problems exactly. It was cumbersome. Wordpress was heavy for what I wanted to do.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
